

MARTIN DUB

ABOUT ME

Hello! I'm 22-year-old student currently at third year of study. I'm communicative and not afraid of responsibility. I don't lack imagination and can handle all kinds of problems. I have a general knowledge and am interested in maths space and IT.

CONTACT



oakk.martin@gmail.com



+420 770 616 800



Kondrac 115 25801 Vlašim



martin-dub



Marvelous Martin





WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - TODAY

CSOB a.s.

Intranet Administrator

2019

IBM Czech Republic

Technology Support Administrator Cloud Support Technician

2018 - 2019

Hemingway Bar Prague Doorman

EDUCATION

2019 - TODAY

Czech University of Life Sciences PragueFaculty of Economics and Management, Informatics

2010 - 2018

Secondary grammar school Vlašim, Tylova 271 General orientation

SKILLS

Microsoft Office 365
Programming Python, C, Java, C#
Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator
HTML, CSS, JS, XML, XSD, XSLT, JSON
Docker, Kubernetes
Hardware knowledge

HOBBIES

Frisbee, Football, Tennis Travelling Collecting limited bottles of alcohol